<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>damiloladolor</title>
    <link>https://0xd0d.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on damiloladolor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 20:38:40 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://0xd0d.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Web scraping with go and go-colly</title>
      <link>https://0xd0d.github.io/posts/web-scraping-with-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 20:38:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xd0d.github.io/posts/web-scraping-with-go/</guid>
      <description>I have been flirting with go for a few weeks now and I built a simple forum-like website using gin which is a popular web framework for golang. After building the application, I was satisfied with how much I was able to learn about the language so I decided to do another little project with it. While I was browsing the web mindlessly(like most of us do), I stumbled upon a comment that talked about web scrapping in python then an idea popped in my mind, why not scrape the frontpage of a popular online forum then use the data to populate my own database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>https://0xd0d.github.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 17:31:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xd0d.github.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello people, this is my first post on my blog, and I hope to write more of posts at least once a week. This is work in progress, I plan to start writing soon on cool things I learn. 🚀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://0xd0d.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 21:24:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xd0d.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Damilola Dolor, a web developer based in Lagos Nigeria and I love to build efficient server-side applications and APIs. I am currently in my final year studying computer engineering at the University of Lagos. I have a nice dog named Rigsby (after one of my favorite characters in the Mentalist) that I love to teach new tricks once in a while, I guess that&amp;rsquo;s where my magical powers come from &amp;ndash; my ablilty to quickly pick up new tricks, skills etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact me</title>
      <link>https://0xd0d.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:28:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xd0d.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can contact me through any the following channels:
 Email Twitter Github  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://0xd0d.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0xd0d.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of some of projects I have worked on and deployed.
  A mini blog
 I learnt about the MVC framework for structuring web projects. This was built using Go and Gin framework. I implmented CRUD operations with mongodb as a database. I implemented Authentication and Authorization using JWT. I deployed the app to heroku    An image sharing platform
 This was built using Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>